Deadlier than ever.
Deep Blue Sea 3 is a action, horror, science
fiction film directed by John Pogue.
Emma Collins and her team are spending their third summer on the island of Little Happy studying the effect of
climate change on the great white sharks who come to the nearby nursery every year to give birth.
Along with the last two inhabitants of this former fishing village, their peaceful life is disrupted when a "scientific" team led by her
ex-boyfriend and marine biologist Richard show up looking for three bull sharks who we soon learn aren't just any bull sharks.
Emma Collins, played by Tania Raymonde.
Richard Lowell, played by Nathaniel Buzolic.
Eugene Shaw, played by Emerson Brooks.
Lucas, played by Bren Foster.
Miya, played by Reina Aoi.
Spin, played by Alexander Bhat.
Deep Blue Sea 3 is a 2020 American science fiction natural horror film
directed by John Pogue and starring Tania Raymonde.
Emma Collins and her team are on Little Happy Island studying the effect of climate change on great white sharks who come to the nearby
nursery every year to give birth, their peaceful life is disrupted when a "scientific" team shows up looking for three bull sharks.
It is the third and final installment of the Deep Blue Sea film
series, and a direct sequel to Deep Blue Sea 2.
The film explores themes of ocean, boat, shark attack, animal attack, sequel.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.